michiganbusiness.us 2008-12-18

# Michigan Business Privacy Policy and External Link Disclaimer

_Last Updated:   March 31, 2008._

The Michigan Business Directory ( [www.michiganbusiness.us](http://www.michiganbusiness.us/) ) website is owned and managed by Nicayla Enterprises, Inc. (NEI).  NEI knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and responsibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting MichiganBusiness.us -   you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

**What data do we collect automatically and why?**

When you visit MichiganBusiness.us and you have not otherwise identified yourself (e.g., via registration with a Nicayla Enterprises, Inc. Site), our web server automatically recognizes your IP address, but not your e-mail address. We collect the IP address and monitor general site use and traffic patterns to improve our web site and the products and services we offer. NEI uses web server logs to collect data for metric purposes. Examples of the types of data collected on the logs are IP addresses, referral pages, date and time of Site access, and Site visited. We may use collected data to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor.

**What happens if I register?**  

Registration is allowed on certain pages of the MichiganBusiness.us website.  When you register your company on the MichiganBusiness.us website,  information can be accessed by other visitors. If you don't want to disclose this information you can leave optional fields blank.  E-mail addresses are necessary for interested parties to contact your company. Providing an incorrect email address in the business profile will disable any e-mail notifications from visitors (i.e. visitors interested in your services or buying your products).  

NEI takes reasonable caution to ensure that your email address is not publicly displayed.  NEI may use company information from it's member businesses to contact them regarding a new service or product that may interest them.  You may request removal  at anytime.

**Online Transactions**

NEI receives online orders for upgrades via a well known and trusted payment option:

PayPal [[read privacy policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)] 

From our payment operator we only receive registration related information, we have no access to credit card numbers or bank account details you provided during purchase.

**Information from Contact Forms and Request for Services**

Technical information obtained while we provide support may be used to train personnel and to create documentation, knowledge base, FAQs and other support materials. No personal information of yours will be published. 

NEI offers online services such as our "Pay Per Lead Program". Some online services require you enter personal identifying information. Any information collected by online services we offer is not disclosed to third parties unless explicitly stated, and it is not used for any purposes not directly related to the functions of the application.

**Newsletter Subscription**

You may be interested in receiving notifications about new services.  We don't send more than one email newsletter per month.  Unsubscribe instructions are provided at the bottom of each message. Removal requests are processed immediately upon reception.

**What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide additional online features.  NEI does not use cookies on the MichiganBusiness.us website. 

  * Some links in on MichiganBusiness.us Web site(s) point to documents and sites which are not located within the internet domains that we manage, therefore they may use cookies. 

**Does GregRobert Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our member businesses is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not share your information with anyone outside of Nicayla Enterprises, Inc. except for authorizing transactions through Paypal. 

**Children**

Nicayla Enterprises, Inc. does not sell products or services for purchase by children.  If you are under 18, you may use our website only with involvement of a parent or guardian. NEI takes reasonable precautions to ensure that companies do not post information that is not safe for people of all ages.  

Visitors are never required to specify age information. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Michigan. If you have any concern about privacy at Nicayla Enterprises, Inc., please send us a thorough description and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

**External Links Disclaimer**

Some links in on MichiganBusiness.us Web site(s) point to documents and sites which are not located within the internet domains that we manage and, therefore, are not controlled by Nicayla Enterprises, Inc. These links are included to point the visitor to other possibly relevant resources.

A link to a document or site other than those included within the domain(s) managed by NEI does not necessarily imply that Nicayla:

  * endorses the organization(s) or person(s) providing them, 

  * agrees with the ideas expressed, or 

  * attests to the correctness, factuality, appropriateness, or legality of the contents.
